{
    "subject": "Jacques_Feyder",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "L'Atlantide__1921_film_",
    "human_readable": "Jacques Feyder directed the film L'Atlantide (1921).",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9069869518280029,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Jacques Feyder."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8976038694381714,
            "question": "What is the title of the film directed by Jacques Feyder?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8459609746932983,
            "question": "Who directed the film L'Atlantide?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6075274348258972,
            "question": "What year was the film L'Atlantide released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5958744287490845,
            "question": "What other films did Jacques Feyder direct?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4462803602218628,
            "question": "What impact did L'Atlantide have on cinema?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4100513756275177,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the plot of L'Atlantide?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32701575756073,
            "question": "Were there any famous actors in L'Atlantide?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3022328019142151,
            "question": "Is L'Atlantide a silent film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2682957947254181,
            "question": "What genre is L'Atlantide likely to be?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Jacques Feyder directed the film L'Atlantide (1921).",
            "html": "yago_8592_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is L'Atlantide a silent film?",
            "html": "yago_8592_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Were there any famous actors in L'Atlantide?",
            "html": "yago_8592_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about the plot of L'Atlantide?",
            "html": "yago_8592_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8592_111.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8592_119.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8592_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8592_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8592_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8592_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8592_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8592_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8592_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8592_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because all the documents provided contain information that confirms Jacques Feyder was indeed the director of the film L'Atlantide (1921), specifically mentioning it in document file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_8592/re-ranker-msmarco/53.txt and other documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that \"L'Atlantide is a 1921 French-Belgian silent film directed by Jacques Feyder,\" which directly supports the statement that Jacques Feyder directed the film L'Atlantide (1921)."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}